<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Authors | Peng Lin</title>
    <link>https://penglin03.github.io/authors/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://penglin03.github.io/authors/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Authors</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>https://penglin03.github.io/img/icon-192.png</url>
      <title>Authors</title>
      <link>https://penglin03.github.io/authors/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://penglin03.github.io/authors/admin/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://penglin03.github.io/authors/admin/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I am a 5th year Ph.D. student in Computer Science at Washington State University (&lt;a href=&#34;http://wsu.edu&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;WSU&lt;/a&gt;), under the supervision of &lt;a href=&#34;https://scholar.google.com/citations?user=9u7wNjUAAAAJ&amp;amp;hl&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Dr. Yinghui Wu&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.eecs.wsu.edu/~holder/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Dr. Lawrence Holder&lt;/a&gt;.
My research interests span the topics of big data analytics, data mining, knowledge graphs, and data quality. Specifically, my recent work on knowledge graphs develops novel models and algorithms to discover missing facts and correct erroneous information, and has demonstrated significant improvement of efficiency and effectiveness for data quality. Beyond my domain, I also extend my work to agriculture planning and collaborates with a research center &lt;a href=&#34;http://cpaas.wsu.edu/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;CPAAS&lt;/a&gt; at WSU. An ongoing project aims to develop a smart irrigation strategy supported by knowledge graph techniques to increase the production and profit of fruits.
The research problems in my Ph.D. research fall under fundamental data management challenge in the era of big data, which plays a crucial role in emerging knowledge-graph-based systems, such as search engine optimization, social networks analysis, natural language processing, and recommendation systems.
Before joining WSU, I got my M.S. and B.S. degrees in Electrical Engineering from Shanghai Jiao Tong University (&lt;a href=&#34;http://en.sjtu.edu.cn/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;SJTU&lt;/a&gt;) in China, and worked three years as a software development engineer at &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.marvell.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Marvell&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
